itviec.com 2017-06-26

# Privacy Policy - ITviec

ITviec is registered at 466/4 Le Quang Dinh, Binh Thanh Dist., Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam. (“ITviec,” “we, us, our”) is a leader in the provision of online recruitment, advertising solutions. ITviec acts as the data controller of personal information obtained from its clients with a need for recruitment services and of personal information submitted by candidates who are interested in job postings.

This privacy policy describes how your data is obtained, processed and forwarded and what your rights are in respect of your personal data.

### Collecting your data

Our main aim is to facilitate the recruitment process, and match our clients’ requirements to IT job opportunities or candidates. In order to fulfil our legal and business obligations we procure personal information you make available to us when visiting our website. We use this information to improve our services we offer to you and to analyze and remedy defects. In order to use our services, you will be asked to provide us with your personal data such as your name, your email address and your Curriculum Vitae.

In the course of recruitment process we may also store further information that may be of importance for a successful placement.

### How do we use your data

To be able to provide our products and services to you, your information will be retained, processed and disclosed by us in the following ways:

  * To facilitate the recruitment process, by matching your details to IT job opportunities;
  * To allow details of your skills and experience, to be viewed by our clients whom we feel may be interested in engaging your services.
  * To allow you to subscribe to our  _“JobMail”_  service. This service will allow you to receive details of latest jobs via e-mail which are relevant to your sector and professional experience. Where you are sent details of a job via  _“JobMail”_  service, you will be able to unsubscribe from such updates at any time with the unsubscribe link at the bottom of every JobMail email,
  * To keep you informed of IT job opportunities and IT contract assignments which we think may be of interest to you;
  * To keep you updated of goods and services provided by our third party business partners which are relevant to your sector. You can opt out at any time from such e-mails itviec+unsub@itviec.com
  * To preserve our business relationship with you as a user of our website;
  * To keep you informed of the products and services (relevant to your sector and your professional interests) offered by us or our group companies via relevant marketing communications. These could include information about recently registered candidates/consultants, client workshops we are arranging, market updates, new software or training courses that may be of interest to you;
  * To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.
  * To notify you about changes to our service.

### Your access rights to your stored data, changes and objections to the data processing

You can contact us at itviec+privacy@itviec.com in the event that you:

  * Have any queries about the information that we hold about you;
  * Wish to inform us of any changes in your information or wish to correct the information we hold about you;
  * Have any requests with regard to our processing of your personal data;
  * Decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive marketing emails from us or our group companies, please either email the above address or follow the unsubscribe link in one of our marketing email messages to you;

### Hyperlinks

Our website may contain links to other websites, which are outside our control and are not covered by this statement. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you, which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours.

### Data quality

We rely on you to ensure that your information is complete, accurate and current. Please do inform us promptly of any changes to or inaccuracies of your information.

### Data retention

We hold your data with a view to providing future recruitment services to you and to manage the business relationship. In the event that the business relationship ceases we confirm that we will delete personal data in accordance with our legal obligations.

### Security measures

We have appropriate technical and organizational security measures in place to ensure the security of your information and to protect it against deliberate or accidental manipulation, destruction, loss or unauthorized access.

Despite our efforts regarding security it is important to bear in mind that the internet is not a secure means of communication. Personal information communicated through the internet may be intercepted by other people. We cannot guarantee the security of personal information sent to us through this website. By using this website and entering your personal data, you accept that you use this website at your own risk.

### Changes to this Policy

We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy at any time solely at our discretion. Any changes we make to our Privacy Policy in future will be posted on this page. We encourage you to check the date of this policy whenever you visit our website for any updates or changes. You may find the date of this policy at the bottom of this page.

#### WHAT ARE COOKIES?

A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we store on your browser or the hard drive of your computer if you agree. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive.

#### WHAT TYPES OF COOKIES DO WE USE?

We use two types of cookies on our website:

 **‘Session Cookies’**  
---  
These are temporary cookies, which only exist in the period you access the website (or more strictly, until you close the browser after accessing the website). Session cookies help our website remember what you chose on the previous page, therefore avoiding having to re-enter information. On our website, these cookies do not contain personal information, and cannot be used to identify you.  
 **‘Persistent Cookies’**  
These are cookies remain on your device after you have visited our website. These cookies help us to identify you as a unique visitor (by storing a randomly generated number).  
  
#### WHY DO WE USE COOKIES?

To tailor our website so that it meets your specific needs, we use different technologies, including cookies, which allow us to distinguish you from other users of our website.

We use cookies:

  * To recognize and count the number of visitors and pages or various parts of a page they have visited on our site;
  * To see how visitors move around the site when they are using it, for example, we use Google Analytics, a popular web analytics service provided by Google Inc. Google Analytics uses cookies to help us to analyze how visitors use our site. This helps us to improve the way our website works, for example, by ensuring that visitors are finding what they are looking for easily. Find out more about how these cookies are used on [Google’s Privacy site](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en).
  * As you browse ITviec.com, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partner, AdRoll, then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with [company website]. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number.  You can visit this [page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) to opt out of AdRoll and their partners’ targeted advertising.

In summary, by using cookies we are able to improve your experience when you browse our website and enable us to continually improve our site and our services for you. Our cookies have been set in our browser and we will assume you are ok with them via your continuous use of our website. You can disable certain cookies as set out below. If you disable these cookies we cannot guarantee how the site will perform for you.

#### MANAGE YOUR COOKIES

Enabling cookies will ensure you receive the optimum user experience from our website.

Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can deactivate this function at any time and set your browser to notify you whenever a cookie is sent. You can use your browser settings to block all or some cookies. Please note that if you do block all cookies you may not be able to access all or parts of our site.

Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can deactivate this function at any time and set your browser to notify you whenever a cookie is sent. You can use your browser settings to block all or some cookies. Please note that if you do block all cookies you may not be able to access all or parts of our site.

Amending your cookie settings is different in different browsers, for ease, we’ve included instructions on amending your settings in the most popular browsers below:

#### OPT-OUT FROM GOOGLE’S DOUBLECLICK

Anyone who prefers not use Google’s DoubleClick cookie can opt out. This opt-out will be specific only to the browser that you are using when you click the “Opt out” button [here](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

#### How to check cookies are enabled on windows platforms

 **Microsoft Internet Explorer**  
Select ‘Tools’ from the top menu of your browser and then select ‘Internet options’, then click on the ‘Privacy’ tab 2. Ensure that your Privacy level is set to Medium or below, which will enable cookies in your browser 3. Settings above Medium will disable cookies

 **Mozilla Firefox**  
1\. Select ‘Tools’ from the top menu of your browser and then select ‘Options’ 2. Then select the Privacy icon 3. Click on Cookies, then select ‘allow sites to set cookies’

 **Google Chrome**  
1\. Select ‘Tools’ from the top menu of your browser and then select ‘Options’ 2. Click the ‘Under the Hood’ tab, locate the ‘Privacy’ section, and select the ‘Content settings’ button 3. Now select ‘Allow local data to be set’

 **Safari**  
1\. Select the cog icon’ from the top menu of your browser and then select ‘Preferences’ 2. Select ‘Security and, check the option that says ‘Block third-party and advertising cookies’ 3. Click ‘Save’ How to check cookies are enabled for apple platforms Microsoft Internet Explorer 5.0 on OSX 1. Select ‘Explorer’ from the top menu of your browser and select ‘Preferences’ options 2 Scroll to the ‘Cookies’ option under Receiving Files 2. Select the ‘Never Ask’ option

 **Safari on OSX**  
1\. Select ‘Safari’ from the top menu of your browser and select the ‘Preferences’ option 2. Click on ‘Security’ then ‘Accept cookies’ 3. Select the ‘Only from site you navigate to’

If you are using a different browser please consult your product documentation, online help files or the browser manufactures website.

 _This policy was updated in January 2014._
